Guide to the Robert Fitch Papers WAG.261
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Subject Files
  - District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (DC37): Real Estate Fund, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (DC37): Reform, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (DC37): Rosenthal v. Roberts, et al., 2004 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (DC37): Roy Commer (Local 375 President), 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (DC37): Roy Commer (Local 375 President): Complaint, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (DC37): Telephone Directories, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (DC37): Turkey Scandal, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (DC37): Turkey Scandal: Indictments, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - District Council 37, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (DC37): William Cutolo (organized crime figure), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Dollars and Democrats, 1984-2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dollars and Democrats: Clippings, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dollars and Democrats: Contributions to Political Campaigns, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Dollars and Democrats: Contributions to Political Campaigns, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Dollars and Democrats: International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades (IBPAT), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Dollars and Democrats: International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Dollars and Democrats: Union Privilege, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Espada, Pedro, Jr. (New York State Senator-elect), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fraser, Steven, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Garment Industry, 1995-2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Garment Industry: Asian American Legal Defense and Education Fund (AALDEF) Suit, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Garment Industry: Chinese Staff and Worker's Association, 1992-2000 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Garment Industry: Corruption, 1993-2005 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Garment Industry: DKNY Class Action Complaint, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Garment Industry: Dov Charney (American Apparel), 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Garment Industry: Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC), 2000 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Garment Industry: Italy, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Garment Industry: Legislation, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Garment Industry: Liz Claiborne, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Garment Industry: New Jersey, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Garment Industry: New York City, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Garment Industry: Notes, 1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Garment Industry: Pensions, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Garment Industry: San Francisco, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Garment Industry: Sweatshops, 1998-2002, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Garment Industry: Sweatshops: 446 Broadway, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Garment Industry: Sweatshops: Clippings, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Garment Industry: Sweatshops: Franz Leichter Report, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Garment Industry: Sweatshops: Kathie Lee, 1991-2004 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Garment Industry: Sweatshops: Luke Loc, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Garment Industry: United Students Against Sweatshops, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - General Motors: Form 5500, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - General Strikes: Europe, 1998-2004 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Genovese Crime Family, 1996-2003 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Gotti, John A., Jr., 1998 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Green, Mark: Preliminary Investigation Into the Parks Department Lifeguard Program, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Hard Hat News, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Health Care: Canada, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Health Insurance Plan of New York (HIP), 1998-2004 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Health Insurance Plan of New York (HIP): Annual Report, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Health Insurance Plan of New York (HIP): Audits, 1982-1987 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Hidden Costs of Capitalism, 2002-2005 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Hidden Costs of Capitalism, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Hollywood, Florida, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE), 1995-2001 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE), 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE), 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE): Chicago, 1997-2003 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE): Chicago, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE): Corruption, 1998-2004 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE): Edward T. Hanley (President), 1998-2003 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE): History, 2001, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE): Jesse Jackson, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE): John Wilhelm, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE): Kurt Muellenberg (Public Review Board Member), 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Iannuzzi, Joseph "Joe Dogs" (organized crime figure), 1985-1994 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Immigration, 2000-2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Impact (newsletter), 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Ironworkers, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - International Association of Machinists (IAM): Buffenbarger, Thomas (President), 2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - International Association of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE), 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - International Association of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE): Local 110, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW): Terry McAuliffe, 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades (IBPAT): District Council 9, 1989-1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades (IBPAT): Glazier's Pension Fund, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1939-1952 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1982-2005 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1983-2002 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1994-2000 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Amerford International Corporation, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Barbara Harvey (Teamsters for a Democratic Union Attorney): Brennan and Bane Hearings, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Barbara Quindel (Election Officer), 1996-2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Barbara Quindel (Election Officer): Reports, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Barry Feinstein (President), 1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Boston, 1991-2001 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Central States Pension Fund, 1998-2004 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Central States Pension Fund: Crisis, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Central States Pension Fund: Employers, 1997-2003 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Chicago, 1978-1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Chicago, 1994-2003 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Chicago, 1988-2001 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Chicago: Jack Ruby, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Chicago: Organized Crime, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Committee on Education and the Workforce, Subcommittee on Oversight and Investigations, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Convoy Dispatch (newsletter), 1986 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Convoy Dispatch (newsletter), 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Convoy Dispatch (newsletter), 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Convoy Dispatch (newsletter), 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Convoy Dispatch (newsletter), 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Convoy Dispatch (newsletter), 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Corruption, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Corruption, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Crescencio Perea (garbage hauler), 2004 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Dan De Santi (President), 2003 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Detroit, 1993-2002 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Elections, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Elections, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Elections Scandal (1996), 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Fear of Reprisals Ends (FORE), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) Reports, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Finances, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Frederick B. Lacey (attorney), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Gene Giacumbo, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Gregory A. Butler Article, undate (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Harold M. Ickes, 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): History, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Independent Review Board (IRB), 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Independent Review Board (IRB), 2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Independent Review Board (IRB) Exhibits, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Independent Review Board (IRB) Reports, 1995, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Jack Ruby, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): James Hoffa, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): James Hoffa: Murder Contract, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): James Hoffa, Jr., 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): James Hoffa, Jr., 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): James Hoffa, Jr.: Corruption, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): James Hoffa, Jr.: Independent Review Board (IRB) Deposition, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): James Hoffa, Jr.: Lion King and Key Profiles, 1998-2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): James Hoffa, Jr.: Report by Ron Carey Campaign, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Javits Center, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): John F. Long: Trial, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Joseph Aligo: Independent Review Board (IRB) Report, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Joseph Lombardo, 1987, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Joseph Padellaro (Ron Carey Aide), 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ken Crowe: "The Vindication of Ron Carey", 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Kenneth Conboy, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Kimberly Kathryn Phillips-Fein Article, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Larry Brennan (President, Joint Council 43), 1993-2000 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Larry Brennan (President, Joint Council 43): Independent Review Board (IRB) Report, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Las Vegas, Nevada, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 25, 1994-2002 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 25, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 97, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 138, 1986-1997 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 138, 1993-2000 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 138: Court Transcript, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 282, 1963, 1993-1998 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 282, 1999-2004 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 282: Leon Olson, 1992-1997 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 282: Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act (RICO) Case, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 295, 1993-2001 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 295: #295 News (newsletter), 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 705, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 707, 1989-2000 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 804, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 806, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 807, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 810, 1987-1999 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Local 814, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Michael Bane: Independent Review Board (IRB) Report`, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Money Laundering, 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): New Jersey, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Pension Funds, 1996-2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Pension Funds: Annual Reports (Form 5500), 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Pension Funds: Local 710, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Peter Menechino, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Philadelphia: Johnny Morris, 1993-2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Richard Trumka, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey, 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey, 1991-1998, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: Articles by Ken Paff, 1992-2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: Articles by Mike Moroney, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: Bernard Fligel (accountant), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: Election Fraud Trial, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: Expulsion (Internal Review Board Report), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: Independent Review Board (IRB) Reports, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: Indictment, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: James Hoffa, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: Money Laundering, 1997-2001 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: Supporters, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: Trial, 1993-2001 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ron Carey: UPS Stock, 1993-1997 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Sun Valley Real Estate Scandal, 1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Teamster.net, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU), 1972-2002 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU), 1991-2000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU), 1999, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Teamsters for a Democratic Union (TDU): Bob Hasegawa, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Ted Katsaros (Local 282), 1980-1995 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Thomas Puccia (attorney), 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Tom Leedham, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Trucking Industry, 1996-2001 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Trusteeships, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): UPS, 1992-2000 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): UPS Strike, 1997-2003 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): United States v. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Appeal, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Vito Locascio: Independent Review Board (IRB) Testimony, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): William T. Hogan: Independent Review Board (IRB) Report, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): William T. Hogan: Independent Review Board (IRB) Testimony, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): William W. Hamilton: Indictment, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Working Conditions, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU): History, 1979-1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU): History, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU): Local 23-25 Contract, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - International Longshore and Warehouse Union (ILWU), 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - International Longshoremen's Association (ILA), 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - International Longshoremen's Association (ILA), 2005 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - International Longshoremen's Association (ILA): Anthony Scotto, 1986-1991 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - International Longshoremen's Association (ILA): Ronald Reagan, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - International Longshoremen's Association (ILA): United States v. International Longshoremen's Association (ILA), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE): Dennis Walton, 1987-1999 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Islamic Fundamentalism, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - J. Anthony Lukas Prize Project, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Kheel, Theodore, 1991-2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Labor History: Articles, 1997-2001, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Labor History: Articles, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Labor History: Articles, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Labor History: Articles and Books, 1929-1936 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Labor History: Articles and Books: Lyon, David Nicholas: "The World of P.J. McGuire", 1972 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Labor History: Banks, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Labor History: Building Trades: Chicago, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Labor History: Chicago Federation of Labor, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Labor History: Dynamiting, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Labor History: Henry George (political economist), 2003 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Labor History: International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Chicago Strike, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Labor History: International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT): Chicago Strike, 1905 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Labor History: International Longshoremen's Association (ILA), 2002 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Labor History: International Longshoremen's Association (ILA): Peter Panto, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Labor History: Knights of Labor, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Labor History: Los Angeles Times Bombing, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Labor History: Meyer Lansky, 1983-2003, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Labor History: New Labor History, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Labor History: Robert P. Brindell, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Labor History: Sam Parks, Jr., 1903 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Labor History: San Francisco: Abraham Ruef, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Labor History: Welfare State, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Labor Unions, 1999-2004 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Labor Unions: Campaign Contributions, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Labor Unions: Corruption, 1995-2005 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Labor Unions: Health Benefits, 1995-2004 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Labor Unions: Los Angeles, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Labor Unions: Racial Discrimination, 1953-1998 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Labor Unions: Salaries, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Labor Unions: Workers' Comments, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA), 1984-1999 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA), 1984-1999 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA), 1984-1999 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA), 1995-2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA), 1998-2005 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Accidents, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America (LIUNA): Alaska Pipeline, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)